{
    "response_code":0,
    "results":[
      {
        "category":"Family",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"What is itay's full name?",
        "correct_answer":"Pantalion Odivelas Macawile",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Tayo Odivelas Macawile","Pantalion Araneta Macawile","Pantalion Macawile"]
      },
      {
        "category":"Family",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"When is Kuya Eric's birthday?",
        "correct_answer":"January 15th",
        "incorrect_answers": ["January 16th","January 17th","January 19th"]
      },
      {
        "category":"Family",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"When will ate come home?",
        "correct_answer":"May 31",
        "incorrect_answers": ["May 30","June 1","June 2"]
      },
      {
        "category":"Family",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"What is mama's favorite color?",
        "correct_answer":"Green",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow","Red","Pink"]
      },
      {
        "category":"Family",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"What is papa's favorite drink?",
        "correct_answer":"Red Horse",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Water","Coke","Wine"]
      },
      {
        "category":"Family",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"When inay's death anniversary?",
        "correct_answer":"November 27",
        "incorrect_answers": ["November 28", "November 29", "November 26"]
      },
      {
        "category":"Family",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"In what year did ate Rinalyn and gwapo Eric got married?",
        "correct_answer":"2014",
        "incorrect_answers": ["2013","2012","2015"]
      },
      {
        "category":"Family",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"What career is most aspired in the family?",
        "correct_answer":"IT",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Farmer","Business woman/man","Tambay"]
      },
      {
        "category":"Family",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"What is my boyfriend's name?",
        "correct_answer":"Tighlat",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Tiglat","Tiggy","Tiger"]
      },
      {
        "category":"Family",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"How old are Renz and Kian?",
        "correct_answer":"17 and 14 respectively",
        "incorrect_answers": ["18 and 14 respectively","17 and 15 respectively","18 and 15 respectively"]
      },
      {
        "category":"Family",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"How old are Renz and Kian?",
        "correct_answer":"17 and 14 respectively",
        "incorrect_answers": ["18 and 14 respectively","17 and 15 respectively","18 and 15 respectively"]
      }
    ]
  }